A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller 3rd papers, Associates, John E. Harr papers FA1219
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Population and Sex Education, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 322)
- Population Speeches, 1960-1965 (Box 35, Folder 323)
- Population Systems Approach, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 324)
- National Service for Youth, 1966-1974 (Box 35, Folder 325)
- National Service for Youth, 1966-1970 (Box 35, Folder 326)
- Business Leaders Meeting on Youth, 1970 December 17 (Box 36, Folder 327)
- Youth Task Force Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 328)
- Youth Task Force Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 329)
- Youth Task Force: Hampshire College Speech, 1970 December (Box 36, Folder 330)
- Youth Statement #3: General Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 36, Folder 331)
- Youth Statement #3: Articles, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 332)
- Hudson Report on Israeli National Service Program, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 333)
- Draft of Israeli National Service Program Report, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 334)
- Youth Task Force Dialogue Week, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 335)
- Youth Task Force Dialogue Week, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 336)
- Youth Task Force Dialogue Week Meeting, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 337)
- Youth Task Force Dialogue Week Meeting, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 338)
- Yankelovich Report on Youth, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 339)
- Common Cause, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 340)
- Youth: Drugs, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 341)
- Youth Task Force: Corporate Responsibility, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 342)
- Youth Task Force: Pioneer Valley Consortium, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 343)
- Youth Task Force: Political Action, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 344)
- Youth Task Force: Public Interest Study Groups, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 345)
- Youth Task Force: Intern Program & Communication Activities, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 346)
- Quality of Life Materials, 1968-1970 (Box 37, Folder 347)
- Background Material for Book: JDR 3rd Study: Explanation of Study, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 348)
- Background Material for Book: JDR 3rd Study for 1951-1952, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 349)
- Background Material for Book: JDR 3rd Study for 1953, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 350)
- Background Material for Book: JDR 3rd Study for 1954-1955, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 351)
- Background Material for Book: JDR 3rd Study for 1956, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 352)
- Background Material for Book: JDR 3rd Study for 1957, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 353)
- Background Material for Book: JDR 3rd Study for 1958, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 354)
- Background Material for Book: List of JDR 3rd Activities during 1946-1949, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 355)
- Background Material for Book: RBF Special Studies Performing Arts Panel, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 356)
- Background Material for Book: Raymond Fosdick's Conversations with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1952-1954 (Box 39, Folder 357)
- Background Material for Book: History of the Property of Rockefeller Center, no date (Box 39, Folder 358)
- Photographs of John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1970s (Box 39, Folder 359)